thelabellife.com 2017-06-07

# privacy policy

This section pertains to the Privacy Policy of TheLabelLife.com owned by The Label Corp Private Limited. We would like to inform that our privacy policy is subject to change without intimation and you shall be required to review the same regularly.

The protection and security of your personal information is one of The Label Corp. Private Limited's top priorities. This Privacy Policy discloses The Label Corp. Private Limited's practice with respect to the information collected from the users of this website. By using this website you agree to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy as well as the website's Terms of Use. By accessing or using this website you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in any manner described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy extends to both, users who visit the website but do not transact business on the website, as well as users who are registered on the website. 'Personal Information' refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact or locate the person, to whom such information pertains including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, identification number, credit card information etc.

PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING TERMS OF OUR PRIVACY POLICY  
PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED

By accepting this privacy policy, you authorize TheLabelLife.com to collect, store and use any information that you provide on our website. The information collected by us are: • All information entered by you on our website such as your name, address, contact number, email ID, chat history, and such other information sent by you via emails to our email ID. • Information collected by means of cookies that are installed on your hard drive. • Information such as the IP Address of your computer, the server from which you are accessing our website, details of web browser and operating system used to access our website, date, time and place of accessing of our website etc.

#### COOKIES

Cookies are small pieces of information saved by your browser onto your computer. Cookies are used to record various aspects of your visit and assist TheLabelLife.com to provide you with uninterrupted service. TheLabelLife.com does not use cookies to save Personal Information for outside uses.

We have implemented Google Analytics features based on Display Advertising (Google Display Network Impression Reporting, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting). Visitors can opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings.

We, along with third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies together to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our site.

No use or services available on this website are directed towards children. TheLabelLife.com does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children or sell its products to children.

#### USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

The Label Corp. Private Limited owns all the information collected via the website or applications installed on the website. As applicable, the information collected by TheLabelLife.com shall be used to contact you about the website and website related news and services available on the website; monitor and improve the website; calculate the number of visitors to the website and to know the geographical locations of the visitors; update you on all the special offers available on the website and provide you with a better shopping experience. This includes sending emails intimating the various offers on the website. You may at any time choose to unsubscribe from such email. Some of your information may be shared with and used by third parties who shall need to have access to information, such as courier companies, credit card processing companies, vendors etc. to enable them and TheLabelLife.com perform their duties and fulfill your order requirements. TheLabelLife.com does not allow any unauthorized persons or organization to use any information that TheLabelLife.com may collect from you through this website. However, TheLabelLife.com is not responsible for any information collected or shared or used by any other third party website due to your browser settings.

The Label Corp.Private Limited reserves the right to share any of your personal information to comply with the orders of subpoenas, court orders or other legal process. Your Personal Information may be disclosed pursuant to such subpoenas, court order or legal process, which shall be without notice to you.

TheLabelLife.com may share collective information such as demographics and website usage statistics with our sponsors, advertisers or other third parties (such third parties do not include TheLabelLife.com's marketing partners and network providers). When this type of information is shared, such parties do not have access to your Personal Information. When you contact TheLabelLife.com through any means such as chat/email, TheLabelLife.com reserves the right to include your email ID for marketing communications. You can unsubscribe from such communications anytime you wish to do so.
